



Ageel Ur Rehman Chishti

Nationality: Pakistani (+92) 3142881710

Date of birth: 20/05/1996

Gender: Male

■ Email address: ageel.chishti@outlook.com

Website: https://aqeelchishti.github.io/

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ageelchishti/

Address: Near Railway Station, Goth Ghani, P/O Khas, 63100 Bahawalpur (Pakistan)

ABOUT ME

I'm currently looking for full-time Penetration Tester or Python/Django Developer job positions. I have 2+ years of freelancing experience in Python/Django & WordPress Development. Moreover, I also have specialized 1+ years of apprenticeship and internship experience in Vulnerability Assessment, Penetration Testing, and Red Teaming Operations. Apart from that, I'm seeking a suitable master's degree abroad in Information Security where I could reinforce my knowledge and skills to contribute in the research & development of information security.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Security Analyst Intern | Internship

Bytesuit LLC [09/2021 - 02/2022]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Penetration Tester & Cyber Operations Training | Apprenticeship

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [08/2020 - 09/2021]

City: Bahawalpur **Country:** Pakistan

Conduct penetration testing on several Live VM Cloud Network Environments, Websites & Web Applications, and then Report on Findings. Including Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing.

Python/Django & WordPress Developer | Freelancing

Fiverr & Upwork [09/2019 – Current]

City: Bahawalpur Country: Pakistan

Working experience of Python/Django Development, WordPress Development, Landing page, Website & Web Application Development, Web Designing, and Python Web Automation and Scraping.



EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Hons.)

National College of Business Administration & Economics (NCBA&E) [16/03/2015 - 31/08/2019]

Address: 31-A Model Town A, Sarwar Shaheed Road, 63100 Bahawalpur (Pakistan)

https://ncbae.edu.pk/

Field(s) of study: Computer Science Final grade: CGPA: 3.50/4.00

Thesis: Marble Crafts Ecommerce Store

DIGITAL SKILLS

Python Web Development & Automation

Python / FLask / Django / Django REST Framework / Object Oriented Programming (OOP) / Django REST Framework / SQL (SQLite PostgreSQL MySQL) / Python Web Automation / Vue Js / Web Scraping / Bootstrap 5 / HT ML5/CSS, Javascript / Svelte Js / Wordpress + Elementor / Javascript (ES6) / Git

Information Security

Penetration Testing / Vulnerability Assessment / Linux (terminal commands, Bash/Shell) / Information Security / C ybersecurity / WPScan / SQLMap / Open Source Intelligence (OSINT) / Penetration Test (Kali tools, Nessus, CVE) / Wireshark / Metasploit Framework / OWASP Top 10 / Burp Suite / Web Application Security Testing / Nessus / Kali Linux / Nmap

HONOURS AND AWARDS

Ethical Hacker Nanodegree

Udacity [29/06/2021]

https://confirm.udacity.com/TLEEUM7L

Penetration Testing, Network Defense & Cyber Operations

National Cyber Training Program (NCTP) [09/2021] https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/pentest-pdf.png https://aqeelchishti.github.io/docs/network_defence-pdf.png

Technical Support Fundamentals

Coursera [13/09/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/9P9ZNB3RYQQ9

The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking

Coursera [30/09/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/V4XW2JFTUNAP

Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User

Coursera [17/10/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/6QP35BAMRN3P

Crash Course on Python

Coursera [25/12/2020]

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/FPRTQQF3KVSM



Linux Command Line professional

Codecademy Pro [05/09/2020]

https://ageelchishti.github.io/docs/Codecademy bash scripting certificate-ageel-chishti.pdf

Python for Security Professional

Cybrary [10/01/2020]

https://ageelchishti.github.io/docs/cybrary-cert-python-for-security-professionals.pdf

Certificate of Proficiency in Information Systems Management (CPISM)

Aptech Computer Education [10/02/2015]

PROJECTS

Bytesuit LLC

[10/2021 - 10/2021]

Information Technology Company Website built with WordPress & Elementor

https://bytesuit.com/

Penetration Testing & Red Teaming Operations Report

[06/2021 - 06/2021]

Working experience in custom VM cloud network environment build testing and live web application [learnaboutsecurity.com] Vulnerability Assessment, Penetration Testing & Red Teaming Operations Report.

https://docs.google.com/document/d/1UnqtlKlbP6CpHX4bYj8lq39i0U2jZAG0aRj0bKogWrA/

Vulnerability Assessment & Penetration Testing Report

[07/2021 - 07/2021]

Working experience in Live VM cloud network environment testing includes Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing.

https://docs.google.com/document/d/157vRs9wI_zlD5tAqvXlZ9sMEnscbZbr5i-xuZqlBsAM/

Field View Contractors

[12/2020 - 12/2020]

Landscape & Construction Company Website built with Python, Django & Bootstrap.

https://fieldviewcontractors.com/

Pakistan Marbles

[10/2019 - 10/2019]

Natural Stone Flooring Company Website built with Python, Django & Bootstrap.

https://pakistanmarbles.herokuapp.com/

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Designing Websites and Web Automation

During my studies, I have done dozens of Web Design and Automation projects. I really enjoy working on it.



Join Pentesting Training Platforms

I really like to join Penetration Testing training platforms and learn with real-world scenarios. I have already joined platforms like Hack The Box and Try Hack Me.

Gaming

I also like playing First Person Shooter games.

Playing Badminton

I'm also a badminton player and I took part in several tournaments on the community level in my local area.